So an Ohio man by the name of Frank E. Tyson died in police custody on April 18th after being
arrested by Canton police officers. Body cam footage of the incident reveals Tyson yelling
I can't breathe and you're on my neck as officers subdued him. Officers pinned him face down on the
ground, ignored his cries of distress, told him to shut the f*** up. One officer can be heard saying
I've always wanted to be in a bar fight. I don't know if this counts. When another officer asked
did he calm down? He was told yeah he might be out. You know Tyson laid motionless for five minutes
before officers checked for a pulse and began CPR. Tyson was dosed twice with Narcan, an opioid overdose
reversal medication but was declared dead at a local hospital. What disturbs me the most these days
is how this feels like it's very connected to Israel and just the way that they treat Palestinians and
the way that they're that they've been treating us here and that there's like this whole ethos
around policing that is very much a psychology that says I can do whatever I want to do because
I'm a police person. I just find it fascinatingly terrible and we always have to ask this question.
We can't allow police brutality to be normalized into just another trending topic so we must continue
to demand systemic change and add it to the list of demands that we have.